<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
	<title>Octavio Maury's Blog</title>
	<link>https://octaviomaury.com/</link>
	<description>Octavio Maury's Home on The Web</description>

	<item>
		<title>gaylist removal and other news</title>
		<link>https://octaviomaury.com/blog-gaylistremoval.html</link>
		<guid>https://octaviomaury.com/blog-gaylistremoval.html</link>
		<description>

  lmao im not even gonna attempt to sugarcoat this, but I got fired from my burger place job, and my it might've  been because of the gaylist on here being so "not PC". so as an attempt to not scare away any future  employers, I've unlisted it from any navigation panels. Of course, I wouldn't ever remove it completely as I
 still think it's funny and im doing this kind of reluctantly. You can still view the gaylist  if you follow
 this hyperlink or if you have it bookmarked,  or if you look at the html files on my Github. I'm hoping to maybe
 at some point in  the future bring it back, but for now, its gonna remain unlisted. I'm gonna keep updating it.
 Don't worry :)

 

  In other news, school let out for summer break, so now I can start workin on the website more than I could've
 with homework breathing down my neck (kidding. I never actually did the homework. STICK IT TO DA MAN!)

 Yesterday, the first day after school let out, I had a power outage for about 7 or 8 hours, and spent most of the
 day in the backyard with my family. at some point it got dark and we were going to bed, and after we had fallen
 asleep,  at exactly 1AM, the power came back, and every light in the house turned on simultaneously. It was
 pretty funny.

 Thats about it.

			Cheers.
		<pubDate>June 27 2021</pubDate>
	</item>


	<item>
		<title>Domain Name</title>
		<link>https://octaviomaury.com/blog-domainname.html</link>
		<guid>https://octaviomaury.com/blog-domainname.html</guid>
		<description>I am now the proud owner of the octaviomaury.com domain, no silly .github.io shit. I'm surprised how cheap I  got it for, actually, it was  only 8$/year. SO from now on, just go to octaviomaury.com for all your octo-related  needs.

 Thats about it.

 Cheers.
	</description>
		<pubDate>June 23 2021</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>The Movie Portal is Up!</title>
		<link>https://octaviomaury.com/blog-movieportalup.html</link>
		<guid>https://octaviomaury.com/blog-movieportalup.html</guid>
		<description>  The Movie Portal is up. Actually, its been done since last night but I was too tired to write a blog post about it.  I'm gonna be postin animations and stuff as well as whatever I feel like lol. Last night I put up this video where  I run a C script. It's pretty cool.

 In other news, I got a job at a burger place, so hopefully I can start buying cool things like skating gear or a  new computer.

 Thats about it.

		Cheers.
	</description>
	<pubDate>May 22 2021</pubDate>
</item>


	<item>
		<title>Blog Post Archive</title>
		<link>https://octaviomaury.com/blog-blogpostarchive.html</link>
		<guid>https://octaviomaury.com/blog-blogpostarchive.html</guid>
		<description> 
 I made a brand-new page on the site. Check it out!
 https://octaviomaury.github.io/blogposts.html

 Very early on in the redesigning of my site, I realized that after a while, the Blog Posts would probably take up  a lot of space on the homepage, and that would probably be a pain in the ass for anyone with slow internet.

 So, making an archive for blog posts has been on my mind for a while now. Turns out it was extraordinarily  easy to do.

 Pretty much everything about making a website is deceptively easy to do.

 So, from now on only 3 blog posts will be shown on the homepage, and if you wanna read older posts, just go  through The Archives

 Another cool thing this new archive allows for is easier sharing, as each post now has it's own url.

 Errrrm that's about it.

 Cheers.
	</description>
	<pubDate>May 13 2021</pubDate>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
